American Association of University Women, Waco Branch records, Inclusive: 1923-2002, undated, Bulk: 1926-1997, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Photographs and Scrapbooks, 1926-2002, undated; 4
  The Photographs and Scrapbooks series, dated 1926-2002, includes limited individual photographs but others incorporated into scrapbooks. Scrapbooks reflect activities and projects pursued by the association from chapter beginning to end. Early chapter history, predominantly newsletters, is most heavily presented in this format rather than throughout other series. There is a gap from 1948-1969 which seems to be consistent with the shortage of records in other parts of the collection. The series is arranged by material type, then chronologically within each type. The series is in good condition.
  Photographic print
  - Photographs: State Conference, San Antonio, Texas, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Photographs: Heart of Texas Regional History Fair, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Photographs: Expanding Your Horizons Science & Math Event, undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Photographs: Garage Sale, undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Scrapbooks: General, 1926-1946 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbooks: General, 1947-1948 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbooks: General, 1969-1975 (Box 4 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbooks: General, 1985-1988 (Box 4 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbooks: General, 1988-2002 (Box 4 OVZ, Folder 3)